Inventory of the Clarissa Sligh Papers, 1950-2012
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Clarissa Sligh papers 1950-2010
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sligh, Clarissa T.
70 linear feet Extent: 51307 Items
Artist and author of works such as Wrongly Bodied, Reading Dick and Jane with Me, What's Happening With Momma? Jake in Transition, and It Wasn't Little Rock. Collection includes materials relating to Sligh's career as an artist, with particular focus on her various projects and exhibitions in the 1980s, 1990s, and early 2000s. Projects represented include Jake In Transition/Wrongly Bodied, Witness to Dissent/It Wasn't Little Rock, Coast to Coast, Sandy Ground, Malcolm X: Man, Ideal, Icon, What's Happening With Momma? and an NC Reunion/Slavery project, along with several others. Sligh's files frequently include correspondence, research materials, drafts of essays and exhibition plans, clippings and other source materials, contact sheets and slides, and occasionally exhibit pieces and texts from the actual installation. Other items included in the collection are exhibition binders and scrapbooks kept by Sligh to document her career; correspondence and communication between Sligh and other artists, galleries, or publishers; catalogs and publicity materials from Sligh's many exhibitions, shows, and publications, artists' books, materials documenting Sligh's art and process, large framed photographic prints; and other materials. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
RL.01207
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
However, collection may contain materials to which the Acknowledgment of Legal Responsibilities and Privacy Rights form applies. Patrons must sign this form before using this collection.
Also, all or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. Consequently, there may be a 24-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Clarissa Sligh Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2011 and 2012.
Biographical Note
Clarissa Sligh is a visual artist, writer, and lecturer. Sligh was born in Washington, D.C., grew up in Arlington, Virginia, lived in Manhattan for 30 years and now resides in the mountains of Asheville, North Carolina. She has taught at New York University, the School of Visual Art and the University of Pennsylvania.
When she was 15 years old she became the lead plaintiff in the 1955 school desegregation case in Virginia (Clarissa Thompson et. al. vs. Arlington County School Board). After working in math and science with NASA and later in business, she began a career as an artist, using photographs, drawings, text, and personal stories to explore themes of transformation and social justice.
In 1988, she published her first artists' book "What's Happening With Momma?" through the Women's Studio Workshop in New York. Additional artists' books include Wrongly Bodied Two, It Wasn't Little Rock, Voyage(r): A Tourist Map to Japan, and Reading Dick and Jane With Me.
Her solo art installations include Witness to Dissent, Sandy Ground, Re(Union), and Passages. Other artistic series include The Masculinity Project, Reframing the Past, Reading Dick & Jane, Suburban Atlanta, and Jake in Transition. A list of selected works as well as background information and images from each project is available on Sligh's website.
Collection Overview
The Clarissa Sligh Papers have been divided into 8 series: Binders and Catalogs, Projects, Correspondence, Journals and Notepads, Photographs, and Artists' Book Dummies and Drafts, Jake in Transition, and Accession 2013-0149.
The Binders and Catalogs series includes a selection of exhibition binders, kept and collected by Sligh as a record of her various projects, events, and exhibits. Also includes press clippings, museum catalogs, and other programming materials. Items have been removed from their original binders.
The Projects series includes files from many of Sligh's art and research projects, relating to a variety of topics such as slavery, civil rights, genealogy, gender studies, and African American history. A "project" may include materials from an installation, artist book, exhibit, or all of these formats. Sligh's work frequently evolved over time and expanded in scope and format. This series also includes files from Sligh's exhibitions and publications. Major projects documented include: NC Reunion and Slavery Project, a film related to the Artists' Call Against U.S. Intervention in Central America, Jake in Transition/Wrongly Bodied, Coast to Coast, Witness to Dissent, Sandy Ground, and Malcolm X: Man, Ideal, Icon.
The Correspondence Series contains three subseries of correspondence: the first has been sorted in loose chronological order according to Sligh's own folder arrangements; the second contains Sligh's self-designated "to do," "answered," "unanswered," and other unsorted correspondence; the third has files that are arranged alphabetically by subject or correspondent's name.
The Journals and Notepads Series includes a set of legal notepads kept by Sligh during the late 1990s. Many entries related to her work on Jake in Transition, but the journals also include Sligh's discussions and reflections on other projects and artwork.
The Photographs Series includes images of artwork and installations by Sligh, portraits of Sligh, and portraits and snapshots of family and friends.
The Artists Books Dummies and Drafts Series includes mockups and drafts from the production of Wrongly Bodied; It Wasn't Little Rock; Malcolm X; Reading Dick and Jane with Me (including "Play with Jane" print); What's Happening with Momma? and alternate version of this book called Girlchild; Hiroshima, Hopes and Dreams; and Voyage(r): Tourist Map to Japan.
The Jake in Transition series consists of photographic prints.
Accession 2012-0149 is an addition consisting of Sligh's documentation of her work and process, photographs and negatives, large screen prints, and political posters.
Subject Headings
Sligh, Clarissa T.; Sligh, Clarissa T. -- What's Happening With Momma?; Nexus Press; Women's Studio Workshop; Artists' books; Artists' books by women; Civil rights movements -- Virginia -- Pictorial works; Collage; Exhibitions; Minority women artists; Mixed media (Art); Sex change -- Pictorial works; Transgender people -- Identity -- Pictorial works; Women artists, Black; Writing and art; Staten Island (New York, N.Y.) -- Historic sites -- Pictorial works; Genealogy -- North Carolina; Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture
Separated Material
Some artists' books by Sligh and others have been separated from this collection to be cataloged independently.
Contents of Collection
- Binders and Catalogs, 1982-2009 and undated, (8 boxes)
  Series includes a selection of exhibition binders, kept and collected by Sligh as a record of her various projects, events, and exhibits. Also includes press clippings, museum catalogs, and other programming materials. Items have been removed from their original binders.
  - Exhibition Binders
    - 1982, 1986, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - 1988, (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - 1989, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 1)
    - 1989, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 2)
    - 1990 Part 1, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - 1990 Part 2, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Witness to Dissent book, 1991, (4 folders) (Box 3)
    - 1991, (3 folders) (Box 3)
    - 1992, (3 folders) (Box 4)
    - 1993, (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - 1994, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 4)
    - 1994, (2 of 2 folders) (Box 5)
    - 1995 (Box 5)
    - 1999-2003, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - 2002-2005, (3 folders) (Box 5)
  - Clippings binder, 1984-2001, (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Events and Programs binders, 1996-2008, (5 folders) (Box 6)
  - Clippings, 1984-2009, (9 folders) (Box 7)
  - Catalogs and publicity, 1987-2009 and undated, (9 folders) (Box 8)
  - Catalogs and Work by Others
    - Faith Ringgold (Box 44)
    - Deborah Willis, (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Other artists, (2 folders) (Box 44)
- Projects, (25 boxes)
  This series includes files from many of Sligh's art and research projects, relating to a variety of topics such as slavery, civil rights, genealogy, gender studies, and African American history. A "project" may include materials from an installation, artist book, exhibit, or all of these formats. Sligh's work frequently evolved over time and expanded in scope and format. This series also includes files from Sligh's exhibitions and publications. Materials have been arranged by project, with general projects listed at the end in alphabetical order.
  - NC Reunion and Slavery Project files
    - African Dancers Group (Box 9)
    - African Dancers Women (Box 9)
    - Clarissa Sligh family tree (Box 9)
    - Correspondence about the Slavery project (Box 9)
    - DoorMeNeg.pct 360 percent (selection) (Box 9)
    - Genealogy of Priscilla Best (Box 9)
    - Genealogical research (Box 9)
    - Huffman Boston High School reunion, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Installation instructions (Re (Union)) (Box 9)
    - Interviews (Box 9)
    - Lemmon Edwards family reunion, 1995 (Box 9)
    - Mel Watkin (Box 9)
    - North Carolina (Box 9)
    - Notes, NC reunion project (Box 9)
    - 100 Years of... (Box 9)
    - Photographs/photocopies from Slavery/Reunion project, (4 folders) (Box 9)
    - Research binder, family history (Box 10)
    - Research, family history (Box 10)
    - Research files (Box 10)
    - Storyboard (Box 10)
    - Books (Civil Rights bills) (Box 11)
    - Genealogy (Box 11)
    - Images (Box 11)
    - Notepads (Box 11)
    - Photographs (Box 11)
    - Research files (Box 11)
    - Sara Lane images (Box 11)
    - Audiotapes, (11 tapes) (Box 12)
    - Reels, (2 reels) (Box 12)
      Access Restricted: Original audiovisual materials are closed to use; access copies must be made. Contact Research Services with questions.
  - Artists' Call
    - Artists' Call, (3 folders) (Box 13)
    - La Verdadera Avenida de las Americas, 1984, (1 VHS and 1 Umatic) (Box 13)
  - Jake in Transition/Wrongly Bodied
    - Clare Cornell, Wrongly Bodied (Box 14)
    - Correspondence with publisher, Wrongly Bodied (Box 14)
    - Ellen Craft research files (Box 14)
    - Essay on Wrongly Bodied (Box 14)
    - Layout notes (Box 14)
    - Leads, Wrongly Bodied (Box 14)
    - Learning to See/Writings about Jake (Box 14)
    - Notes and drafts (Box 14)
    - Photographing Jake (Box 14)
    - Publishing, Wrongly Bodied (Box 14)
    - Thumbnails: Jake's Body, Clarissa's Body (Box 14)
    - Texas Women's University thesis: Masculinity (Box 14)
    - Research files (Box 14)
    - Loose notes re: Jake Project (Box 15)
    - Notepads (Box 15)
  - Coast to Coast
    - Addresses, (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Agendas, 1989-1992 (Box 16)
    - Ancestors Known and Unknown: Box Works (Box 16)
    - Ancestors essays and slides (Box 16)
    - Art-in-General, 1989 (Box 16)
    - Artemisia Gallery, Chicago (Box 16)
    - Artist Books Anthology (Box 16)
    - Artist correspondence (Box 16)
    - Artists letter drafts (Box 16)
    - Artist letter copies (Box 16)
    - Artists resumes (Box 16)
    - Black women artists: End Our Isolation (Box 17)
    - Book contact sheets and negatives (Box 17)
    - Book pages xeroxes (Box 17)
    - Cook slides (Box 17)
    - Box Art history (Box 17)
    - Box contact sheets (Box 17)
    - Box project contacts - photographs (Box 17)
    - Box project notes (Box 17)
    - Box Show negatives (Box 17)
    - Center for Book Arts (Box 17)
    - DiverseWorks, Texas (Box 17)
    - Emergency Fund Artists, 1989 (Box 17)
    - Eubie Blake Cultural Center (Box 17)
    - Evergreen exhibition agreement, 1991 (Box 17)
    - Exhibit catalogs, 1990-1991 (Box 17)
    - Exhibition checklist, 1992 (Box 18)
    - Exhibition correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 18)
    - Faith Ringgold (Box 18)
    - Flossie Martin Gallery correspondence, May 1990 (Box 18)
    - Franklin Furnace (Box 18)
    - Funding (Box 18)
    - Grant applications, 1987-1988 (Box 18)
    - Islip (Box 18)
    - Jerome Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 18)
    - Leadership development (Box 18)
    - Margaret Gallegoes (Box 18)
    - Michigan (Box 18)
    - Networking workshop (Box 18)
    - Participants (Box 19)
    - Press packet (Box 19)
    - Project proposal (Box 19)
    - Proposals, 1987-1988 (Box 19)
    - Proposals and budgets (Box 19)
    - Quilt Squares (Box 19)
    - Radford, Virginia (Box 19)
    - Receipts, 1995 (Box 19)
    - Rejin (Box 19)
    - Travelling exhibit (Box 19)
    - Volunteer letters (Box 19)
    - What's Happening with Momma? contacts and negatives (Box 19)
    - Wisconsin (Box 19)
    - Women's Caucus for Art, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Witness to Dissent
    - Arlington School Integration (Box 20)
    - Big face paper positive (Box 20)
    - Binder with source material, (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - Burling, Edward (Box 20)
      - Article and materials (Box 20)
      - Letters (copies) (Box 20)
      - Letters (originals), 1957-1962 (Box 20)
    - Clarissa and Ann Marx paper positives (Box 20)
    - Clippings, 1956-1961 (Box 20)
    - Clippings, 1957-1968 (Box 20)
    - Clippings (Box 20)
    - Clippings from exhibit (Box 21)
    - Collages/xeroxes (Box 21)
    - Contributions, 1991-1992, (4 folders) (Box 21)
    - Contributions by visitors, (4 folders) (Box 21)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Court briefs (Box 21)
    - Dorothy Hamm, re: 25th anniversary of Arlington integration, 1984-1986 (Box 21)
    - Drafts of form letters to participants, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Exhibition agreements, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Exhibit photocopies (Box 22)
    - Exhibit preparation materials, (4 folders) (Box 22)
    - 4 People on Courthouse steps (enlargement) (Box 22)
    - History of Negro Violence (Box 22)
    - Image enlargements (Box 22)
    - Installation information (Box 22)
    - Interview release forms, 1990 (Box 23)
    - "It Wasn't Little Rock" text (Box 23)
    - Letters to contributors, 1991 (Box 23)
    - Notepads kept by Sligh (Box 23)
    - Publicity and promotional materials (Box 23)
    - Source materials (Box 23)
    - 3 figures at entrance to AIG (Box 23)
    - Thompson vs. Co. School Board of Arlington County, photocopies, 1956 (Box 23)
    - Timeline drafts (Box 23)
    - Exhibit items
      - Books with race-related laws, (5 folders) (Box 24)
      - Clippings (Box 24)
      - Exhibit pieces and text (Box 24)
      - Scroll (Box 25)
      - Exhibit pieces and text, (6 folders) (Box 26)
      - Scrapbook of clippings (Box 26)
      - Exhibit videos, (3 VHS) (Box 12)
  - Sandy Ground
    - Boats from Staten Island (Box 27)
    - Houses from Staten Island (Box 27)
    - Notepad (Box 27)
    - Photocopies and notes (Box 27)
    - Photographs (Box 27)
    - Plaque from installation (Box 27)
    - Sketches and maps (Box 27)
    - Snug Harbor materials (Box 27)
    - Snug Harbor passages, (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - Sources and maps (Box 27)
    - Texts, (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - The Hunter's Grave, read by Alton Fitzgerald White, (1 audiocassette) (Box 27)
  - Malcolm X: Man, Ideal, Icon
    - Binder, (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - Checklist (Box 28)
    - Clippings (Box 28)
    - Exhibit folder and timeline (Box 28)
    - Malcolm/Martin photocopies and photographs (Box 28)
    - Photographs and slides (Box 28)
    - Walker Art Center, 1992 (Box 28)
    - Installation in Progress, other materials, 1992-1994, (1 VHS) (Box 28)
  - Projects, general
    - Arizona (Box 29)
    - Articles and reviews (Box 29)
    - Atlanta Suburban South Project, (2 folders) (Box 24)
    - Baltimore, Maryland Institute (Box 29)
    - Black photographer's exhibition (Box 29)
    - Bodywork videotape work, 1997 (Box 29)
    - Bookbinding (Box 29)
    - Borowsky - Little Rock Book (Box 29)
    - Brandywine (Box 29)
    - Chaney, Goodman, Schwerner (Box 29)
    - Civil Rights clippings (Box 29)
    - Civil Rights interviews: VSW Exhibit research, 1990 (Box 34)
    - Civil Rights interviews: VSW Exhibit research, (2 audiocassettes) (Box 12)
    - Coast Print, Maria Elena, 1995 (Box 29)
    - College transcripts (Box 29)
    - Contemporary Women Artists: New York, Indiana State University, 2005 (Box 29)
    - Crafts Museum (Box 29)
    - Creative Capital, 2004 (Box 29)
    - Susan Crowe (Box 29)
    - Current exhibitions, 1997-1999 (Box 29)
    - Directories (Box 29)
    - Drawings with N. (photographs) (Box 29)
    - Essays, 2005 (Box 29)
    - Experimental Narrative in Artists Books, Louisiana State University (Box 29)
    - Former students (Box 30)
    - Hampton exhibition, 1999, (2 folders) (Box 30)
    - Holy Cross (Box 30)
    - Howard University (Box 30)
    - Howard University thesis: Constructing Black Masculinity, 1999, (3 folders) (Box 30)
    - ICP-Bard (Box 30)
    - ICP exhibition (Box 30)
    - Interview with T., April 2000 (Box 30)
    - It Wasn't Little Rock, (3 folders) (Box 30)
    - Legal illustrations (Box 31)
    - Norman Lewis materials (Box 31)
    - Lists, slides art work, 1991-1994 (Box 31)
    - Lists of slides, 1997-2000 (Box 31)
    - Lists of works, (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Loan forms and exhibitions (Box 31)
    - Masculinity: In Transition from Female to Male (Box 31)
    - Masculinity/Men project (Box 31)
    - McBee Shoot Journal, April 1997 (Box 31)
    - Moving party (Box 32)
    - Moving Philadelphia information (Box 32)
    - National Millennium survey, 2000 (Box 32)
    - No Racial Pattern: Black Churches Burning, Richmond, Virginia, 1999, (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - No Racial Pattern: Black Churches Burning, (1 Hi8 and 1 audiocassette) (Box 12)
    - Notes, 2002 (Box 32)
    - Noyes Museum (Box 32)
    - Obsessions, Ceres Gallery (Box 32)
    - Other writings, 1996 (Box 32)
    - Pindell, Howardena (Box 32)
    - Presentation notes, 1991-2003, (2 folders) (Box 32)
    - Press releases (Box 32)
    - Press releases, other artists (Box 32)
    - Publication correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 32)
    - Reading with Dick and Jane and Me (Box 32)
    - Resumes (Box 32)
    - Rhode Island College (Box 32)
    - Saturday Night/Sunday Morning Exhibition, 2003 (Box 33)
    - Schedules, 2001-2005 (Box 33)
    - School journal pages, 1996 (Box 33)
    - School of Visual Arts, 2002 (Box 33)
    - Script Video with Philip Brookman and Debra Singer, 1999 (Box 33)
    - Serious works (Box 33)
    - Strong Medicine transcript, 1994 (Box 33)
    - Strong Medicine (for E.H.M.), (1 VHS tape) (Box 12)
    - Talley, Dan (Box 33)
    - Teaching for Change, 2004 (Box 33)
    - Texas Tech, Lubbock, 2001 (Box 33)
    - Texas Women's University final papers (Box 33)
    - 3 Rivers Arts Festival, Pittsburgh, 1999 (Box 33)
    - Transforming the White Man's Bible, 2008 (Box 28)
    - Travelogue, 1993 (Box 33)
    - Virginia Center for Creative Arts residency application, 2000 (Box 33)
    - VSW, Summer 1999 (Box 33)
    - VSW workshop, 2004 (Box 33)
    - World Book Dealers.com, 2002 (Box 33)
    - Writings, 1990-1991 (Box 33)
- Correspondence, 1981-2006, (7 boxes)
  The correspondence series contains three subseries of correspondence: the first has been sorted in loose chronological order according to Sligh's own folder arrangements; the second contains Sligh's self-designated "to do," "answered," "unanswered," and other unsorted correspondence; the third has files that are arranged alphabetically by subject or correspondent's name.
  - Chronological files
    - 1981-1991 (Box 35)
    - 1989-1996 (Box 36)
    - 1992-1998 (Box 37)
    - 1998-2006 (Box 38)
  - Unsorted correspondence (Box 38)
  - Name or Subject files
    - A (Box 39)
    - A-M (Box 40)
    - M-Z (Box 41)
- Journals and notepads, 1995-2004, (2 boxes)
  Series includes a set of legal notepads kept by Sligh during the late 1990s. Many entries related to her work on Jake in Transition, but the journals also include Sligh's discussions and reflections on other projects and artwork.
  - Journals, 1995-1997 (Box 42)
  - Journals, 1997-2000, 2004, and undated (Box 43)
  - Self-portrait sketchbooks, 1982 and undated, (2 books) (Box 45)
  - Journal and notes from Jake In Transition/Wrongly Bodied, 2000-2001 (Box 45)
- Photographs, (2 boxes)
  - Images of artwork by Sligh, (4 folders) (Box 46)
  - Portraits of Sligh (Box 46)
  - Photographs of Angela's wedding, 1989 (Box 46)
  - Binder of portraits of Sligh, friends, and family, (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - "Clarissa" binder with photocopies of photographs, 1958-1961 (Box 47)
- Artists Books Dummies and Drafts, (6 boxes)
  The Artists Books Dummies and Drafts Series includes mockups and drafts from the production of Wrongly Bodied; It Wasn't Little Rock; Malcolm X; Reading Dick and Jane with Me (including "Play with Jane" print); What's Happening with Momma? and alternate version of this book called Girlchild; Hiroshima, Hopes and Dreams; and Voyage(r): Tourist Map to Japan. The series does not include published versions of these works.
  - Wrongly Bodied (Box 48)
  - It Wasn't Little Rock (Box 49)
  - Malcolm X (Box 50)
  - It Wasn't Little Rock (Box 50)
  - Play with Jane (Box 50)
  - Reading Dick and Jane with Me (Box 50)
  - What's Happening with Momma? (Box 51)
  - Girlchild (Box 51)
  - Hiroshima (Box 52)
  - Voyage(r): Tourist Map to Japan (Box 53)
- Jake in Transition prints, 1996-2001, (23 boxes, 7 large framed prints)
  Prints in boxes 54-66 are 16x20" gelatin silver prints; Prints in box 67 are 22 1/2x17" inkjet on Arches paper; prints in boxes 69-76 are 11x22 1/2" inkjet on Arches paper; Prints 1-7 are Iris prints
  - Deb with Dog, October 1996 (Box 54)
  - March 1, 1997. (Box 54)
  - March 25, 1997. (Box 55)
  - March 30, 1997. (Box 55)
  - With Mirror, April 13, 1997. (2 prints) (Box 56)
  - On Bed, March, 1999. (Box 57)
  - On couch, April 13, 1997. (Box 57)
  - Three-Quarters Body, June 1, 1997. (Box 58)
  - Three-Quarters Body, June 1, 1997. (Box 58)
  - Walking in Yard, September 1997. (Box 59)
  - Flexing Muscles, October 1997. (Box 59)
  - On Telephone, October 1997. (Box 60)
  - Desert Storm T-shirt, September 1997. (Box 60)
  - At Fence, October 1997. (Box 61)
  - At Potter's Wheel #1, October 1997. (Box 62)
  - Testosterone Shot, April 24, 1997. (Box 63)
  - After Wedding, February 2000. (Box 63)
  - Photographing Jake March 1999. (Box 64)
  - Driving Truck, November, 1997. (Box 64)
  - Wedding in Progress, February 2000. (Box 65)
  - Jake and Matt, March 1999. (Box 65)
  - After Lunch, November 1997. (Box 66)
  - Sandwich, October 1997. (Box 66)
  - Attorney at Law, 2001 (Inkjet on Arches paper 22 1/2 x 17) (Box 67)
  - Counseling Work/Medical Doctor, 2001. (Box 67)
  - Wall Panel 16x20" (Box 68)
  - My Own Breast Surgery, 2001. (Box 69)
  - Alice, 2001. (Box 69)
  - Kitchen, 2001. (Box 70)
  - Clay Work, 2001. (Box 70)
  - Jake Weight Training, 2001. (Box 71)
  - Living Room, 2001. (Box 71)
  - Me and Jake, 2001. (Box 72)
  - Jake with Friends, March, 1999. (Box 72)
  - Shaving, 2001. (Box 73)
  - Laying on Bed, 2001. (Box 73)
  - Fall, 1996, 2001. (Box 74)
  - March 25, Video,, 2001. (Box 74)
  - My Weight Training, 2001. (Box 75)
  - March 1, 1997. (Box 75)
  - March 25, 1997. (Box 76)
  - I Got a High Boot of Energy, 2001, 24 1/2 x 17" (Box 76, Print 1)
  - Is This a Real Option?, 2001, 25x21" (Box 76, Print 2)
  - Straight Man (I Know What That Feels Like), 2001, 26x21" (Box 76, Print 3)
  - Tried to Fit (I Didn't Fit That Either), 2001, 26x21" (Box 76, Print 4)
  - God Mistake (I Never Felt I Fit), 2001, 24x21" (Box 76, Print 5)
  - Transition Time Line, 2001, 26x21" (Box 76, Print 6)
  - Couldn't Wait to See (This Is Who Jake Is), 2001, 26x21" (Box 76, Print 7)
- Accession (2012-0149),1985-2012, (35 boxes)